<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="107">
    <author>Squallqt</author>
    <version>1.2.0.0</version>
    <title>
        <en>Invoices</en>
        <fr>Factures</fr>
        <de>Rechnungen</de>
        <es>Facturas</es>
        <it>Fatture</it>
        <pt>Faturas</pt>
        <br>Faturas</br>
        <nl>Facturen</nl>
        <pl>Faktury</pl>
        <ru>Счета</ru>
        <cz>Faktury</cz>
        <cs>发票</cs>
        <ct>發票</ct>
        <hu>Számlák</hu>
        <ro>Facturi</ro>
        <tr>Faturalar</tr>
        <da>Fakturaer</da>
        <no>Fakturaer</no>
        <sv>Fakturor</sv>
        <fi>Laskut</fi>
        <uk>Рахунки</uk>
        <jp>請求書</jp>
        <kr>청구서</kr>
        <vn>Hóa Đơn</vn>
        <id>Faktur</id>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en><![CDATA[Create, send and manage invoices between farms in multiplayer.

Ideal for agricultural contractor gameplay. Bill other farms for services performed: plowing, harvesting, transport, animal care, equipment rental, and 50+ predefined work types. Base prices are aligned with the game's contract economy and automatically adjusted based on your economic difficulty setting. The user can modify any price directly when creating an invoice.

Features:
- Full invoice wizard: select recipient farm, work types, fields, quantities and prices
- Realistic VAT system based on French fiscal law (4 rate groups, editable per line item)
- HT / VAT / TTC breakdown displayed on each invoice
- Simulated VAT setting: when ON, client pays TTC, provider receives HT; when OFF, no VAT applied
- Separate Income and Expense entries in the Finance tab
- Incoming and outgoing invoice tabs with status tracking
- Pay or delete invoices with automatic financial integration
- Automatic payment reminders
- Savegame persistent, fully synchronized in multiplayer
- 25 languages supported

GitHub repository: https://github.com/Squallqt/FS25_Invoices

Access via the dedicated tab in the InGame Menu (ESC).

Changelog:

1.2.0.0:
- Rebalance all base prices to match FS25 contract economy (verified in-game)
- Fix rounding errors in price calculations (field area precision)
- Fix hourly rate hierarchy (driving < transport < delivery)
- Fix wizard state persistence after cancel
- Fix payment float comparison for exact amounts
- Fix farm selection cursor persistence in wizard step 1
1.1.0.0:
- Add VAT system with 4 rate groups based on French fiscal law
- Add adjustable VAT rate per invoice line
- Add HT / VAT / TTC breakdown on invoices
- Add simulated VAT setting (General Settings, ON by default)
- Add payment reminders toggle (General Settings, ON by default)
- Add separated Income and Expense in Finance tab
- Improve UI
- Fix input focus loss when editing invoice fields
1.0.0.0:
- Initial release]]></en>
        <fr><![CDATA[Créez, envoyez et gérez des factures entre fermes en multijoueur.

Idéal pour le gameplay de type ETA (Entreprise de Travaux Agricoles). Facturez les autres fermes pour les prestations réalisées : labour, récolte, transport, soins aux animaux, location de matériel, et plus de 50 types de travaux prédéfinis. Les prix de base sont alignés sur l'économie des contrats du jeu et s'ajustent automatiquement selon le niveau de difficulté économique. L'utilisateur peut modifier librement chaque prix lors de la création d'une facture.

Fonctionnalités :
- Assistant de création complet : choix du destinataire, des travaux, des champs, quantités et prix
- Système de TVA réaliste basé sur la fiscalité française (4 groupes de taux, modifiable par ligne)
- Décomposition HT / TVA / TTC affichée sur chaque facture
- Option TVA simulée : quand activée, le client paie TTC et le prestataire reçoit HT ; quand désactivée, pas de TVA
- Lignes Recettes et Dépenses séparées dans l'onglet Finance
- Onglets factures reçues et émises avec suivi des statuts
- Règlement ou suppression des factures avec intégration financière automatique
- Rappels de paiement automatiques
- Sauvegarde persistante, synchronisation complète en multijoueur
- 25 langues supportées

Dépôt GitHub : https://github.com/Squallqt/FS25_Invoices

Accès via l'onglet dédié dans le menu en jeu (ECHAP).

Changelog :

1.2.0.0 :
- Rééquilibrage de tous les prix de base pour correspondre à l'économie des contrats FS25 (vérifié en jeu)
- Correction des erreurs d'arrondi dans les calculs de prix (précision de la surface)
- Correction de la hiérarchie des tarifs horaires (conduite < transport < livraison)
- Correction de la persistance de l'état du wizard après annulation
- Correction de la comparaison des montants de paiement pour les montants exacts
- Correction de la persistance du curseur de sélection ferme dans l'étape 1
1.1.0.0 :
- Ajout du système de TVA avec 4 groupes de taux selon la fiscalité française
- Ajout du taux de TVA modifiable par ligne de facture
- Ajout de la décomposition HT / TVA / TTC sur les factures
- Ajout de l'option TVA simulée (Paramètres généraux, ON par défaut)
- Ajout de l'option rappels de paiement (Paramètres généraux, ON par défaut)
- Ajout des lignes Recettes et Dépenses dans l'onglet Finance
- Amélioration de l'interface
- Correction de la perte de focus lors de la saisie dans les champs de facture
1.0.0.0 :
- Publication initiale]]></fr>
        <de><![CDATA[Erstellen, senden und verwalten Sie Rechnungen zwischen Betrieben im Mehrspielermodus.

Ideal für Lohnunternehmer-Gameplay. Stellen Sie anderen Betrieben Rechnungen für erbrachte Leistungen: Pflügen, Ernten, Transport, Tierpflege, Maschinenverleih und über 50 vordefinierte Arbeitstypen. Die Grundpreise sind an die Vertragswirtschaft des Spiels angepasst und werden automatisch nach wirtschaftlichem Schwierigkeitsgrad skaliert. Der Benutzer kann jeden Preis bei der Rechnungserstellung frei ändern.

Funktionen:
- Vollständiger Rechnungsassistent: Empfänger, Arbeitstypen, Felder, Mengen und Preise wählen
- Realistisches MwSt-System nach französischem Steuerrecht (4 Satzgruppen, pro Zeile bearbeitbar)
- Netto / MwSt / Brutto-Aufschlüsselung auf jeder Rechnung
- Simulierte MwSt-Einstellung: wenn AN, zahlt der Kunde brutto, der Dienstleister erhält netto; wenn AUS, keine MwSt
- Getrennte Einnahmen- und Ausgabenposten im Finanz-Tab
- Tabs für eingehende und ausgehende Rechnungen mit Statusverfolgung
- Rechnungen bezahlen oder löschen mit automatischer Finanzintegration
- Automatische Zahlungserinnerungen
- Spielstand-persistent, vollständig synchronisiert im Multiplayer
- 25 Sprachen unterstützt

GitHub-Repository: https://github.com/Squallqt/FS25_Invoices

Zugriff über den eigenen Tab im InGame-Menü (ESC).

Changelog:

1.2.0.0:
- Alle Grundpreise an die FS25-Vertragswirtschaft angepasst (im Spiel verifiziert)
- Rundungsfehler bei Preisberechnungen behoben (Feldflächenpräzision)
- Stundensatz-Hierarchie korrigiert (Fahren < Transport < Lieferung)
- Wizard-Zustand nach Abbruch korrigiert
- Zahlungsvergleich bei exakten Beträgen behoben
- Cursor-Persistenz bei Farmauswahl in Schritt 1 behoben
1.1.0.0:
- MwSt-System mit 4 Satzgruppen nach französischem Steuerrecht hinzugefügt
- MwSt-Satz pro Rechnungszeile anpassbar
- Netto / MwSt / Brutto-Aufschlüsselung auf Rechnungen hinzugefügt
- Simulierte MwSt-Einstellung hinzugefügt (Allgemeine Einstellungen, Standard: AN)
- Zahlungserinnerungen-Einstellung hinzugefügt (Allgemeine Einstellungen, Standard: AN)
- Einnahmen und Ausgaben getrennt im Finanz-Tab
- Verbesserungen der Benutzeroberfläche
- Fokusverlust bei der Eingabe in Rechnungsfeldern behoben
1.0.0.0:
- Erstveröffentlichung]]></de>
        <es><![CDATA[Crea, envía y gestiona facturas entre granjas en multijugador.

Ideal para el estilo de juego de contratista agrícola. Factura a otras granjas por los servicios realizados con más de 50 tipos de trabajo predefinidos. Los precios base se ajustan automáticamente según el nivel de dificultad económica, y el usuario puede modificar cualquier precio al crear una factura.

Novedades v1.1:
- Sistema de IVA simulado con 4 grupos de tipos impositivos
- Desglose Sin IVA / IVA / IVA incluido en cada factura
- Separación de Ingresos y Gastos en la pestaña de finanzas
- Recordatorios de pago automáticos
- 25 idiomas soportados
- Corrección de la pérdida de foco al editar campos de factura

Repositorio GitHub: https://github.com/Squallqt/FS25_Invoices

Acceso desde la pestaña dedicada en el menú del juego (ESC).]]></es>
        <it><![CDATA[Crea, invia e gestisci fatture tra aziende agricole in multiplayer.

Ideale per il gameplay da contoterzista. Fattura altre aziende per i servizi svolti con oltre 50 tipi di lavoro predefiniti. I prezzi base vengono regolati automaticamente in base al livello di difficoltà economica, e l'utente può modificare liberamente ogni prezzo durante la creazione della fattura.

Novità v1.1:
- Sistema IVA simulato con 4 gruppi di aliquote
- Dettaglio Escl. IVA / IVA / IVA inclusa su ogni fattura
- Separazione Ricavi e Spese nella scheda finanze
- Promemoria pagamento automatici
- 25 lingue supportate
- Correzione della perdita di focus durante la modifica dei campi fattura

Repository GitHub: https://github.com/Squallqt/FS25_Invoices

Accesso tramite la scheda dedicata nel menu di gioco (ESC).]]></it>
        <pl><![CDATA[Twórz, wysyłaj i zarządzaj fakturami między gospodarstwami w trybie wieloosobowym.

Idealne do rozgrywki w stylu usług rolniczych. Wystawiaj faktury za wykonane prace z ponad 50 predefiniowanymi rodzajami prac. Ceny bazowe dostosowują się automatycznie do poziomu trudności ekonomicznej, a użytkownik może dowolnie modyfikować każdą cenę podczas tworzenia faktury.

Nowości w v1.1:
- Symulowany system VAT z 4 grupami stawek
- Rozbicie Netto / VAT / Brutto na każdej fakturze
- Osobne wpisy Przychody i Wydatki w zakładce finanse
- Automatyczne przypomnienia o płatności
- 25 języków
- Naprawiono utratę fokusa przy edycji pól faktury

Repozytorium GitHub: https://github.com/Squallqt/FS25_Invoices

Dostęp przez dedykowaną kartę w menu gry (ESC).]]></pl>
        <ru><![CDATA[Создавайте, отправляйте и управляйте счетами между фермами в многопользовательском режиме.

Идеально для геймплея сельскохозяйственного подрядчика. Выставляйте счета другим фермам за выполненные работы с более чем 50 предустановленными видами работ. Базовые цены автоматически корректируются в зависимости от уровня экономической сложности, а пользователь может свободно изменять любую цену при создании счёта.

Новинки v1.1:
- Система НДС с 4 группами ставок
- Разбивка Без НДС / НДС / С НДС на каждом счёте
- Раздельные Доход и Расход во вкладке финансов
- Автоматические напоминания об оплате
- 25 языков
- Исправлена потеря фокуса при редактировании полей счёта

Репозиторий GitHub: https://github.com/Squallqt/FS25_Invoices

Доступ через вкладку в игровом меню (ESC).]]></ru>
    </description>
    <iconFilename>icon_Invoices.dds</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true" />

    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="scripts/Main.lua" />
    </extraSourceFiles>
    <l10n filenamePrefix="l10n/l10n" />
</modDesc>