<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="107">
    <author>Squallqt</author>
    <version>1.1.0.0</version>
    <title>
        <en>Invoices</en>
        <fr>Factures</fr>
        <de>Rechnungen</de>
        <es>Facturas</es>
        <it>Fatture</it>
        <pt>Faturas</pt>
        <br>Faturas</br>
        <nl>Facturen</nl>
        <pl>Faktury</pl>
        <ru>Счета</ru>
        <cz>Faktury</cz>
        <cs>发票</cs>
        <ct>發票</ct>
        <hu>Számlák</hu>
        <ro>Facturi</ro>
        <tr>Faturalar</tr>
        <da>Fakturaer</da>
        <no>Fakturaer</no>
        <sv>Fakturor</sv>
        <fi>Laskut</fi>
        <uk>Рахунки</uk>
        <jp>請求書</jp>
        <kr>청구서</kr>
        <vn>Hóa Đơn</vn>
        <id>Faktur</id>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en><![CDATA[Create, send and manage invoices between farms in multiplayer.

Ideal for agricultural contractor gameplay. Bill other farms for services performed: plowing, harvesting, transport, animal care, equipment rental, and 50+ predefined work types. Base prices are aligned with the game's contract economy and automatically adjusted based on your economic difficulty setting. The user can modify any price directly when creating an invoice.

Features:
- Full invoice wizard: select recipient farm, work types, fields, quantities and prices
- Realistic VAT system based on French fiscal law (4 rate groups, editable per line item)
- HT / VAT / TTC breakdown displayed on each invoice
- Simulated VAT setting: when ON, client pays TTC, provider receives HT; when OFF, no VAT applied
- Separate Income and Expense entries in the Finance tab
- Incoming and outgoing invoice tabs with status tracking
- Pay or delete invoices with automatic financial integration
- Automatic payment reminders
- Savegame persistent, fully synchronized in multiplayer
- 25 languages supported

GitHub repository: https://github.com/Squallqt/FS25_Invoices

Access via the dedicated tab in the InGame Menu (ESC).

Changelog:

1.1.0.0:
- Add product selection on the Goods line item with auto-price from in-game market
- Add VAT system (rate per line item, simulated VAT option can be disabled in Game Settings)
- Add option to disable payment reminders (can be disabled in Game Settings)
- Add late fees on unpaid invoices (can be disabled in Game Settings)
- Add separated Income and Expense in Finance tab
- Rebalance all prices to match game contract economy
- Improve user interface
- Fix price and quantity input fields in invoice wizard
1.0.0.0:
- Initial release]]></en>
        <fr><![CDATA[Créez, envoyez et gérez des factures entre fermes en multijoueur.

Idéal pour le gameplay de type ETA (Entreprise de Travaux Agricoles). Facturez les autres fermes pour les prestations réalisées : labour, récolte, transport, soins aux animaux, location de matériel, et plus de 50 types de travaux prédéfinis. Les prix de base sont alignés sur l'économie des contrats du jeu et s'ajustent automatiquement selon le niveau de difficulté économique. L'utilisateur peut modifier librement chaque prix lors de la création d'une facture.

Fonctionnalités :
- Assistant de création complet : choix du destinataire, des travaux, des champs, quantités et prix
- Système de TVA réaliste basé sur la fiscalité française (4 groupes de taux, modifiable par ligne)
- Décomposition HT / TVA / TTC affichée sur chaque facture
- Option TVA simulée : quand activée, le client paie TTC et le prestataire reçoit HT ; quand désactivée, pas de TVA
- Lignes Recettes et Dépenses séparées dans l'onglet Finance
- Onglets factures reçues et émises avec suivi des statuts
- Règlement ou suppression des factures avec intégration financière automatique
- Rappels de paiement automatiques
- Sauvegarde persistante, synchronisation complète en multijoueur
- 25 langues supportées

Dépôt GitHub : https://github.com/Squallqt/FS25_Invoices

Accès via l'onglet dédié dans le menu en jeu (ECHAP).

Changelog :

1.1.0.0 :
- Ajout de la sélection de produit sur la ligne Fournitures (prix automatique depuis le marché)
- Ajout du système de TVA (taux par ligne, option simulée désactivable dans les Paramètres du jeu)
- Ajout de l'option pour désactiver les rappels de paiement (désactivable dans les Paramètres du jeu)
- Ajout des pénalités de retard sur les factures impayées (désactivable dans les Paramètres du jeu)
- Ajout des lignes Recettes et Dépenses dans l'onglet Finance
- Rééquilibrage de tous les prix pour correspondre à l'économie du jeu
- Amélioration de l'interface
- Correction de la saisie dans les champs prix et quantité
1.0.0.0 :
- Publication initiale]]></fr>
        <de><![CDATA[Erstellen, senden und verwalten Sie Rechnungen zwischen Betrieben im Mehrspielermodus.

Ideal für Lohnunternehmer-Gameplay. Stellen Sie anderen Betrieben Rechnungen für erbrachte Leistungen: Pflügen, Ernten, Transport, Tierpflege, Maschinenverleih und über 50 vordefinierte Arbeitstypen. Die Grundpreise sind an die Vertragswirtschaft des Spiels angepasst und werden automatisch nach wirtschaftlichem Schwierigkeitsgrad skaliert. Der Benutzer kann jeden Preis bei der Rechnungserstellung frei ändern.

Funktionen:
- Vollständiger Rechnungsassistent: Empfänger, Arbeitstypen, Felder, Mengen und Preise wählen
- Realistisches MwSt-System nach französischem Steuerrecht (4 Satzgruppen, pro Zeile bearbeitbar)
- Netto / MwSt / Brutto-Aufschlüsselung auf jeder Rechnung
- Simulierte MwSt-Einstellung: wenn AN, zahlt der Kunde brutto, der Dienstleister erhält netto; wenn AUS, keine MwSt
- Getrennte Einnahmen- und Ausgabenposten im Finanz-Tab
- Tabs für eingehende und ausgehende Rechnungen mit Statusverfolgung
- Rechnungen bezahlen oder löschen mit automatischer Finanzintegration
- Automatische Zahlungserinnerungen
- Spielstand-persistent, vollständig synchronisiert im Multiplayer
- 25 Sprachen unterstützt

GitHub-Repository: https://github.com/Squallqt/FS25_Invoices

Zugriff über den eigenen Tab im InGame-Menü (ESC).

Changelog:

1.1.0.0:
- Produktauswahl für Waren-Positionen mit automatischem Spielmarktpreis
- MwSt-System (Steuersatz pro Zeile, simulierte MwSt deaktivierbar in den Spieleinstellungen)
- Option zum Deaktivieren der Zahlungserinnerungen (deaktivierbar in den Spieleinstellungen)
- Verzugsgebühren bei unbezahlten Rechnungen (deaktivierbar in den Spieleinstellungen)
- Einnahmen und Ausgaben getrennt im Finanz-Tab
- Alle Preise an die Spielvertragswirtschaft angepasst
- Benutzeroberfläche verbessert
- Eingabefelder für Preis und Menge korrigiert
1.0.0.0:
- Erstveröffentlichung]]></de>
        <es><![CDATA[Crea, envía y gestiona facturas entre granjas en multijugador.

Ideal para el estilo de juego de contratista agrícola. Factura a otras granjas por los servicios realizados con más de 50 tipos de trabajo predefinidos. Los precios base se ajustan automáticamente según el nivel de dificultad económica, y el usuario puede modificar cualquier precio al crear una factura.

Changelog:

1.1.0.0:
- Selección de producto en líneas de Suministros con precio automático del mercado
- Sistema de IVA (tipo por línea, IVA simulado desactivable en los Ajustes del juego)
- Opción para desactivar los recordatorios de pago (desactivable en los Ajustes del juego)
- Penalizaciones por retraso en facturas impagadas (desactivable en los Ajustes del juego)
- Ingresos y Gastos separados en la pestaña de finanzas
- Reequilibrio de todos los precios según la economía del juego
- Mejora de la interfaz
- Corrección de los campos de entrada de precio y cantidad
1.0.0.0:
- Primera versión

Repositorio GitHub: https://github.com/Squallqt/FS25_Invoices

Acceso desde la pestaña dedicada en el menú del juego (ESC).]]></es>
        <it><![CDATA[Crea, invia e gestisci fatture tra aziende agricole in multiplayer.

Ideale per il gameplay da contoterzista. Fattura altre aziende per i servizi svolti con oltre 50 tipi di lavoro predefiniti. I prezzi base vengono regolati automaticamente in base al livello di difficoltà economica, e l'utente può modificare liberamente ogni prezzo durante la creazione della fattura.

Changelog:

1.1.0.0:
- Selezione prodotto sulla voce Forniture con prezzo automatico dal mercato
- Sistema IVA (aliquota per riga, IVA simulata disattivabile nelle Impostazioni di gioco)
- Opzione per disattivare i promemoria di pagamento (disattivabile nelle Impostazioni di gioco)
- Penali per ritardo sulle fatture non pagate (disattivabile nelle Impostazioni di gioco)
- Ricavi e Spese separati nella scheda finanze
- Ribilanciamento di tutti i prezzi secondo l'economia del gioco
- Miglioramento dell'interfaccia
- Correzione dei campi di inserimento prezzo e quantità
1.0.0.0:
- Prima versione

Repository GitHub: https://github.com/Squallqt/FS25_Invoices

Accesso tramite la scheda dedicata nel menu di gioco (ESC).]]></it>
        <pl><![CDATA[Twórz, wysyłaj i zarządzaj fakturami między gospodarstwami w trybie wieloosobowym.

Idealne do rozgrywki w stylu usług rolniczych. Wystawiaj faktury za wykonane prace z ponad 50 predefiniowanymi rodzajami prac. Ceny bazowe dostosowują się automatycznie do poziomu trudności ekonomicznej, a użytkownik może dowolnie modyfikować każdą cenę podczas tworzenia faktury.

Changelog:

1.1.0.0:
- Wybór produktu dla pozycji Materiały z automatyczną ceną z rynku gry
- System VAT (stawka na wiersz, symulowany VAT można wyłączyć w Ustawieniach gry)
- Opcja wyłączenia przypomnień o płatności (można wyłączyć w Ustawieniach gry)
- Kary za opóźnienie na niezapłaconych fakturach (możliwość wyłączenia w Ustawieniach gry)
- Przychody i Wydatki osobno w zakładce finanse
- Zrównoważenie wszystkich cen do ekonomii gry
- Ulepszenie interfejsu
- Naprawiono pola wprowadzania ceny i ilości
1.0.0.0:
- Pierwsza wersja

Repozytorium GitHub: https://github.com/Squallqt/FS25_Invoices

Dostęp przez dedykowaną kartę w menu gry (ESC).]]></pl>
        <ru><![CDATA[Создавайте, отправляйте и управляйте счетами между фермами в многопользовательском режиме.

Идеально для геймплея сельскохозяйственного подрядчика. Выставляйте счета другим фермам за выполненные работы с более чем 50 предустановленными видами работ. Базовые цены автоматически корректируются в зависимости от уровня экономической сложности, а пользователь может свободно изменять любую цену при создании счёта.

Changelog:

1.1.0.0:
- Добавлен выбор продукта для позиции Товары (цена автоматически из рынка игры)
- Система НДС (ставка на строку, симулированный НДС отключается в Настройках игры)
- Опция отключения напоминаний об оплате (отключается в Настройках игры)
- Штрафы за просрочку на неоплаченных счетах (отключается в Настройках игры)
- Разделение Доходов и Расходов во вкладке финансов
- Перебалансировка всех цен под экономику игры
- Улучшение интерфейса
- Исправлены поля ввода цены и количества
1.0.0.0:
- Первая версия

Репозиторий GitHub: https://github.com/Squallqt/FS25_Invoices

Доступ через вкладку в игровом меню (ESC).]]></ru>
    </description>
    <iconFilename>icon_Invoices.dds</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true" />

    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="scripts/Main.lua" />
    </extraSourceFiles>
    <l10n filenamePrefix="l10n/l10n" />
</modDesc>