<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="107">
    <author>Squallqt</author>
    <version>1.1.1.0</version>
    <title>
        <en>Invoices</en>
        <de>Rechnungen</de>
        <fr>Factures</fr>
        <pl>Faktury</pl>
        <br>Faturas</br>
        <cs>发票</cs>
        <ct>發票</ct>
        <cz>Faktury</cz>
        <da>Fakturaer</da>
        <es>Facturas</es>
        <fi>Laskut</fi>
        <hu>Számlák</hu>
        <id>Faktur</id>
        <it>Fatture</it>
        <jp>請求書</jp>
        <kr>청구서</kr>
        <nl>Facturen</nl>
        <no>Fakturaer</no>
        <pt>Faturas</pt>
        <ro>Facturi</ro>
        <ru>Счета</ru>
        <sv>Fakturor</sv>
        <tr>Faturalar</tr>
        <uk>Рахунки</uk>
        <vn>Hóa đơn</vn>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en><![CDATA[Create, send and manage invoices between farms in multiplayer.

Ideal for agricultural contractor gameplay, this mod lets you bill other farms for your services (plowing, harvesting, transport, animal care, etc.), as well as sell vehicles and consumables directly via invoice.

Base prices are aligned with the game's contract economy and automatically adjusted based on your economic difficulty setting. Each price can be freely modified when creating an invoice.

Features:
- Full creation wizard: choose recipient, work types, fields, quantities and prices
- Vehicle selection with automatic ownership transfer and automatic resale pricing
- Consumable selection (bales, pallets, bigbags…) with automatic ownership transfer and automatic resale pricing
- Product selection with automatic market pricing
- VAT system (4 rate groups, editable per line item, simulated option can be disabled)
- Net / VAT / Gross breakdown displayed on each invoice
- Incoming and outgoing invoice tabs with status tracking
- Pay or delete invoices with automatic financial integration
- Separate Income and Expense entries in the Finance tab
- Automatic payment reminders and late fees
- 25 languages supported
- Compatible with FS25_RedTape: invoice transactions are properly categorized as taxable income and deductible expenses

Important: Only consumables physically present in the world (not stored inside buildings) can be invoiced and transferred. Make sure to eject bales, pallets or bigbags from storage buildings before creating an invoice.

Issues & suggestions: https://github.com/Squallqt/FS25_Invoices

Access via the dedicated tab in the InGame Menu (ESC).

Changelog:

1.1.1.0:
- Fix vehicle and modded fill type icons not displayed in invoice details on receiving client (multiplayer)
- Fix title separator now shrinks to text width on Product, Vehicle and Consumable dialogs
1.1.0.0:
- Add consumable selection (bales, pallets, bigbags…) with automatic ownership transfer and automatic resale pricing
- Add vehicle selection with automatic ownership transfer and automatic resale pricing
- Add product selection for the Products work type with automatic market pricing
- Add VAT system (rate per line item, simulated option can be disabled in Game Settings)
- Add option to disable payment reminders (can be disabled in Game Settings)
- Add late fees on unpaid invoices (can be disabled in Game Settings)
- Add separate Income and Expense entries in the Finance tab
- Add FS25_RedTape integration: invoice income and expenses are categorized for tax calculations
- Rebalance all prices to match game economy
- Significantly improve user interface
- Fix price and quantity input fields
- Existing invoices from v1.0 are fully preserved on update
1.0.0.0:
- Initial release]]></en>
        <de><![CDATA[Erstellen, versenden und verwalten Sie Rechnungen zwischen Betrieben im Mehrspielermodus.

Ideal für Lohnunternehmer-Gameplay. Mit diesem Mod können Sie anderen Betrieben Ihre Dienstleistungen in Rechnung stellen (Pflügen, Ernten, Transport, Tierpflege usw.) sowie Fahrzeuge und Verbrauchsmaterialien direkt per Rechnung verkaufen.

Die Grundpreise orientieren sich an der Vertragswirtschaft des Spiels und werden automatisch an den wirtschaftlichen Schwierigkeitsgrad angepasst. Jeder Preis kann bei der Rechnungserstellung frei geändert werden.

Funktionen:
- Vollständiger Erstellungsassistent: Empfänger, Arbeitstypen, Felder, Mengen und Preise auswählen
- Fahrzeugauswahl mit automatischem Eigentümerwechsel und automatischer Wiederverkaufsbewertung
- Verbrauchsmaterialauswahl (Ballen, Paletten, Bigbags…) mit automatischem Eigentümerwechsel und automatischer Wiederverkaufsbewertung
- Produktauswahl mit automatischem Marktpreis
- MwSt-System (4 Satzgruppen, pro Zeile bearbeitbar, simulierte Option deaktivierbar)
- Netto / MwSt / Brutto-Aufschlüsselung auf jeder Rechnung
- Tabs für eingehende und ausgehende Rechnungen mit Statusverfolgung
- Rechnungen bezahlen oder löschen mit automatischer Finanzintegration
- Getrennte Einnahmen und Ausgaben im Finanz-Tab
- Automatische Zahlungserinnerungen und Verzugsgebühren
- 25 Sprachen unterstützt
- Kompatibel mit FS25_RedTape: Rechnungstransaktionen werden korrekt als steuerpflichtiges Einkommen und abzugsfähige Ausgaben kategorisiert

Wichtig: Nur Verbrauchsmaterialien, die sich physisch in der Welt befinden (nicht in Gebäuden gelagert), können fakturiert und übertragen werden. Stellen Sie sicher, dass Ballen, Paletten oder Bigbags aus Lagergebäuden entnommen werden, bevor Sie eine Rechnung erstellen.

Issues & Vorschläge: https://github.com/Squallqt/FS25_Invoices

Zugriff über den eigenen Tab im InGame-Menü (ESC).

Changelog:

1.1.1.0:
- Fahrzeug- und gemoddete Fülltyp-Symbole werden nun in den Rechnungsdetails beim empfangenden Spieler korrekt angezeigt (Mehrspielermodus)
- Titeltrennlinie passt sich jetzt an die Textbreite an in den Dialogen Produkt, Fahrzeug und Verbrauchsmaterial
1.1.0.0:
- Verbrauchsmaterialauswahl hinzugefügt (Ballen, Paletten, Bigbags…) mit automatischem Eigentümerwechsel und automatischer Wiederverkaufsbewertung
- Fahrzeugauswahl hinzugefügt mit automatischem Eigentümerwechsel und automatischer Wiederverkaufsbewertung
- Produktauswahl für den Arbeitstyp Produkte mit automatischem Marktpreis hinzugefügt
- MwSt-System hinzugefügt (Steuersatz pro Zeile, simulierte Option deaktivierbar in den Spieleinstellungen)
- Option zum Deaktivieren der Zahlungserinnerungen hinzugefügt (deaktivierbar in den Spieleinstellungen)
- Verzugsgebühren bei unbezahlten Rechnungen hinzugefügt (deaktivierbar in den Spieleinstellungen)
- Getrennte Einnahmen und Ausgaben im Finanz-Tab hinzugefügt
- FS25_RedTape-Integration hinzugefügt: Rechnungseinnahmen und -ausgaben werden für die Steuerberechnung kategorisiert
- Alle Preise an die Spielwirtschaft angepasst
- Benutzeroberfläche signifikant verbessert
- Eingabefelder für Preis und Menge korrigiert
- Bestehende Rechnungen aus v1.0 bleiben beim Update vollständig erhalten
1.0.0.0:
- Erstveröffentlichung]]></de>
        <fr><![CDATA[Créez, envoyez et gérez des factures entre fermes en multijoueur.

Idéal pour le gameplay de type ETA (Entreprise de Travaux Agricoles), ce mod permet de facturer les autres fermes pour vos prestations (labour, récolte, transport, soins aux animaux, etc.), mais aussi de vendre des véhicules et des consommables directement par facture.

Les prix de base sont alignés sur l'économie des contrats du jeu et s'ajustent automatiquement selon le niveau de difficulté économique. Chaque prix peut être modifié librement lors de la création d'une facture.

Fonctionnalités :
- Interface de création complète : choix du destinataire, des travaux, des champs, quantités et prix
- Sélection de véhicules avec transfert automatique de propriétaire et prix de revente automatique
- Sélection de consommables (balles, palettes, bigbags…) avec transfert automatique de propriétaire et prix de revente automatique
- Sélection de produits avec prix du marché automatique
- Système de TVA (4 groupes de taux, modifiable par ligne, option simulée désactivable)
- Décomposition HT / TVA / TTC affichée sur chaque facture
- Onglets factures reçues et émises avec suivi des statuts
- Règlement ou suppression des factures avec intégration financière automatique
- Lignes Recettes et Dépenses séparées dans l'onglet Finance
- Rappels de paiement automatiques et pénalités de retard
- 25 langues supportées
- Compatible avec FS25_RedTape : les transactions de factures sont correctement catégorisées comme revenus imposables et dépenses déductibles

Important : Seuls les consommables physiquement présents dans le monde (non stockés dans les bâtiments) peuvent être facturés et transférés. Assurez-vous de sortir les balles, palettes ou bigbags des bâtiments de stockage avant de créer une facture.

Issues & suggestions: https://github.com/Squallqt/FS25_Invoices

Accès via l'onglet dédié dans le menu en jeu (ECHAP).

Changelog :

1.1.1.0 :
- Correction de l'affichage des icônes de véhicules et des fill types moddés dans les détails de facture côté client réception (multijoueur)
- Correction du séparateur de titre qui s'ajuste désormais à la largeur du texte sur les fenêtres Produit, Véhicule et Consommable
1.1.0.0 :
- Ajout de la sélection de consommables (balles, palettes, bigbags…) avec transfert automatique de propriétaire et prix de revente automatique
- Ajout de la sélection de véhicules avec transfert automatique de propriétaire et prix de revente automatique
- Ajout de la sélection de produits pour le type Produits avec prix du marché automatique
- Ajout du système de TVA (taux par ligne, option simulée désactivable dans les Paramètres du jeu)
- Ajout de l'option pour désactiver les rappels de paiement (désactivable dans les Paramètres du jeu)
- Ajout des pénalités de retard sur les factures impayées (désactivable dans les Paramètres du jeu)
- Ajout des lignes Recettes et Dépenses dans l'onglet Finance
- Ajout de l'intégration FS25_RedTape : les revenus et dépenses de factures sont catégorisés pour le calcul des impôts
- Rééquilibrage de tous les prix pour correspondre à l'économie du jeu
- Amélioration significative de l'interface
- Correction de la saisie dans les champs prix et quantité
- Les factures créées en v1.0 sont intégralement conservées lors de la mise à jour
1.0.0.0 :
- Publication initiale]]></fr>
        <pl><![CDATA[Twórz, wysyłaj i zarządzaj fakturami między gospodarstwami w trybie wieloosobowym.

Idealny do rozgrywki w stylu usług rolniczych. Ten mod pozwala wystawiać faktury innym gospodarstwom za wykonane usługi (orka, zbiory, transport, opieka nad zwierzętami itp.), a także sprzedawać pojazdy i materiały eksploatacyjne bezpośrednio przez fakturę.

Ceny bazowe są dostosowane do ekonomii kontraktów w grze i automatycznie skalowane w zależności od poziomu trudności ekonomicznej. Każdą cenę można dowolnie modyfikować podczas tworzenia faktury.

Funkcje:
- Pełny kreator tworzenia: wybór odbiorcy, rodzajów prac, pól, ilości i cen
- Wybór pojazdów z automatycznym przeniesieniem własności i automatyczną wyceną odsprzedaży
- Wybór materiałów eksploatacyjnych (bele, palety, bigbagi…) z automatycznym przeniesieniem własności i automatyczną wyceną odsprzedaży
- Wybór produktów z automatyczną ceną rynkową
- System VAT (4 grupy stawek, edytowalny na wiersz, opcja symulowana możliwa do wyłączenia)
- Rozbicie Netto / VAT / Brutto wyświetlane na każdej fakturze
- Zakładki faktur przychodzących i wychodzących ze śledzeniem statusów
- Opłacanie lub usuwanie faktur z automatyczną integracją finansową
- Oddzielne pozycje Przychody i Wydatki w zakładce Finanse
- Automatyczne przypomnienia o płatności i kary za opóźnienie
- 25 obsługiwanych języków
- Kompatybilny z FS25_RedTape: transakcje fakturowe są prawidłowo kategoryzowane jako dochód podlegający opodatkowaniu i koszty uzyskania przychodu

Ważne: Tylko materiały eksploatacyjne fizycznie obecne w świecie gry (nie przechowywane w budynkach) mogą być fakturowane i przenoszone. Upewnij się, że bele, palety lub bigbagi zostały wyjęte z budynków magazynowych przed utworzeniem faktury.

Issues & sugestie: https://github.com/Squallqt/FS25_Invoices

Dostęp przez dedykowaną zakładkę w menu gry (ESC).

Changelog:

1.1.1.0:
- Naprawiono wyświetlanie ikon pojazdów i zmoddowanych typów wypełnień w szczegółach faktury po stronie odbiorcy (tryb wieloosobowy)
- Separator tytułu dopasowuje się teraz do szerokości tekstu w oknach Produkt, Pojazd i Materiał eksploatacyjny
1.1.0.0:
- Dodano wybór materiałów eksploatacyjnych (bele, palety, bigbagi…) z automatycznym przeniesieniem własności i automatyczną wyceną odsprzedaży
- Dodano wybór pojazdów z automatycznym przeniesieniem własności i automatyczną wyceną odsprzedaży
- Dodano wybór produktów dla typu Produkty z automatyczną ceną rynkową
- Dodano system VAT (stawka na wiersz, opcja symulowana możliwa do wyłączenia w Ustawieniach gry)
- Dodano opcję wyłączenia przypomnień o płatności (możliwość wyłączenia w Ustawieniach gry)
- Dodano kary za opóźnienie na niezapłaconych fakturach (możliwość wyłączenia w Ustawieniach gry)
- Dodano oddzielne pozycje Przychody i Wydatki w zakładce Finanse
- Dodano integrację z FS25_RedTape: przychody i wydatki z faktur są kategoryzowane do obliczeń podatkowych
- Zrównoważenie wszystkich cen zgodnie z ekonomią gry
- Znaczące ulepszenie interfejsu
- Korekta pól wprowadzania ceny i ilości
- Istniejące faktury z v1.0 są w pełni zachowane po aktualizacji
1.0.0.0:
- Pierwsza wersja]]></pl>
    </description>
    <iconFilename>icon_Invoices.dds</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true" />

    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="scripts/Main.lua" />
    </extraSourceFiles>
    <l10n filenamePrefix="l10n/l10n" />
</modDesc>